我为什么还要参加这种家庭会议
Why do I still have to come to these family meetings?
我都是成年人了
I'm an adult.
中午才从地下室起床出来的人
She said, emerging from the basement
还好意思说这种话
in her pajamas at noon.
别烦我 今天可是周六
Get off my back. It's Saturday.
没错吧
Right?
咱们开会要讨论什么
What is this meeting about?
鸭子回来了吗 如果是的话就太诡异了
Are the ducks back? Cause that was weird.
是他们救了我们
They saved us.
脑子正常的应该都不会这么想吧
From people thinking we're normal.
你们妈妈下周一
Your mom starts her new job
就要正式接管外公的衣柜公司了
running grandpa's closet company on Monday,
你知道她每次遇到大事都会干什么
and you know how she gets when there are big changes.
敲敲门
Knockity-knock!
不 千万别
Oh, no. Not --
克拉特沃斯夫人
Mrs. Clutterworth.
谁准备好把家里不用的东西
Who's ready to take everything we don't want
收拾好扔进篮子里
and toss it in the bin?
我准备好了
I am!
你抓手 我抓腿
You get her arms, I'll get her legs.
当孩子们还小的时候
I created Mrs. Clutterworth
我创造了克拉特沃斯夫人这个角色
when the kids were little
好让清理杂物变得有趣一些
as a way to make home organizing fun.
有趣 有趣死了
So fun. Super fun.
或许还有点让人困惑
Maybe a little confusing.
为什么
Why?
你这个名字很明显是改编自
Well, the name is clearly inspired
巴特沃斯夫人[糖浆品牌]
by Mrs. Butterworth, right?
但是说话为什么带英音
But somehow she has a British accent.
因为当时他们很喜欢《欢乐满人间》
Yeah, well, the kids were super into Mary Poppins back then.
还是不理解为什么
Still missing a step.
把这些都拿回自己的房间
Take one of these things up to your rooms.
把你们不用的东西都放进去
Put everything in it you don't use.
我们就不能下周末再做吗 或者永远不做
Can't we just do this next weekend, or, like, never?
不行
No.
我马上就要开始新的工作
I am starting my new job
我想让家里尽可能的整洁
and I want to leave things as organized as possible.
可是大部分人只会把不用的东西扔进柜子里
Most people just throw stuff into a closet.
作为衣柜公司的老板
As president of a closet company,
你应该最清楚这点啊
you should know that.
别狡辩了
We're doing this.
何况 如果你们
Or, more to the point, if...
*如果家里有什么东西*
*There's something that you have*
*是你从来不用的*
*And you never, ever use it*
*把它放进篮子里*
*Put it in the bin*
*一切都扔扔扔*
*Lose it, lose it, lose it*
我觉得你的理智也已经被你扔掉了
Oh, I think you've lost it, lost it, lost it.
我想在老爸退休的第一天敬他一杯酒
I'd like to toast my dad on his first day of retirement.
祝贺你花了42年在柜里
Congratulations on 42 years in the closet...
做生意
business.
我觉得以后最怀念的
I think what I'm going to miss the most
就是那些有关衣柜的笑话了
is all the closet jokes.
一般来说 在这种感性时刻
Traditionally on an occasion this emotionally significant,
主人公都要发表一些感言
the man of the hour delivers a few well-chosen words.
我想告诉你们的是
I would just like to say...
我要去学打高尔夫了
I'm going golfing.
老爸 别忘了莉莉第一场长笛独奏
Dad, don't forget Lily's first flute recital
时间定在周四的三点半
is on Thursday at 3:30.
我很想去给她捧场
I would love to be there,
但是我公司那里走不开
but I'm really swamped at Wo--
这个借口现在不管用了
hell, that snuck up on me.
没事的 外公 我也不想你来
It's okay, Grandpa. I don't want you to come.
我吹得糟透了
I stink.
不 不是的
Hey, no. No.
你才不糟呢
You do not stink.
我不知道为什么她就是这么糟
I don't know why she's so bad.
她明明师出名门啊
She has a great teacher.
我的横笛吹得棒极了
I was a brilliant flautist--
我当时在凡吐拉举办的爵士音乐会上
may have won best new soloist
拿了最佳独奏奖
at the lower Ventura jazz happening.
我以前都把奖杯放在储物柜里
I used to keep my trophy in my locker.
每次那些嫉妒的人把我塞进柜子里
I'd stare at it every time the jealous kids
我都会紧盯着它
would stuff me in there.
祝你今天过得愉快
Hey, have fun today.
你看起来真棒
Nice face candy.
尤其是你的飞行员墨镜
The aviators.
你会是高尔夫球场上最帅的
You're gonna be the coolest guy on the golf course.
过来
Hey, come here.
我必须得跟什么人说一下
I'm dying to tell somebody.
我能跟你说个秘密吗
Can I let you in on a little secret?
秘密 就你和我吗
A secret? Just you and me?
抱歉 憋不住那种奸笑 你继续
Sorry, that had to come out. Go on.
我不是去学高尔夫
I'm not going golfing.
我是去学开飞机
I'm taking my first flying lessons today.
我一直想当一个飞行员
I always dreamed of being a pilot.
杰 太棒了 我理解你
Oh, Jay, that's fantastic, and I-I totally get it.
我以前在老家时
I had a crush on the pilot
暗恋过一个开飞机喷农药的人
who flew the crop duster back home.
他有着宽厚的肩膀 低沉沙哑的声音
He had big, broad shoulders and a deep, husky voice
现在想想 他可能是因为农药污染才声音沙哑
that, in retrospect, could have been pesticide-related.
不要跟任何人说 尤其是歌洛莉亚
Don't tell anyone, especially Gloria.
我想把这事当成惊喜
I want it to be a surprise.
什么都不说
Not a word.
我不会说的
I'm your man.
你背着一个女士挎包
You're wearing a purse.
这是男士的战术挎包
This is a gentleman's tactical tote.
而且你要知道
And I'll have you know,
这个包的同款被一个海豹六队的人背过
this exact model was carried by a member of Seal Team 6.
是啊 他女朋友试裙子的时候他帮着背过一下
Yes, while his girlfriend tried on dresses.
敲敲门
Knockity-knock!
你们在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
用低廉的价格享受沙龙级的剪发
Getting salon-quality haircuts at a fraction of the price!
谢谢你 阿吸
Thanks, Flowbee!
别闹了
Come on, guys.
你们就没有东西要扔吗
Have you gotten rid of anything today?
都在这里了
Yeah, all that.
就一只袜子吗
That's one sock.
天哪
Oh, my goodness.
我们居然想丢掉它
What in the world were we thinking?
来吧 美女 给我一个吻
Hey, gorgeous! Gimme a kiss!
我可不想让卢克的脏袜子碰到我的嘴
I do not want Luke's dirty sock anywhere near my mouth.
那可不止是脏了
It's seen worse.
太恶心了 不
No. Oh, no.
别闹了 专心一点
Come on, guys. Stay focused.
我不能是这个家里唯一有东西要扔的人
I can't be the only one getting rid of stuff today.
你为什么把阿鸡放进来
Wait a minute. What is Chickie doing in there?
因为它已经坏了
It's broken.
可是当孩子们还小的时候
But every year when the kids were little
他可是复活节的明星
he was the star of Easter!
当然耶稣最受欢迎
I mean, besides Jesus.
当你挤他的时候 他会说
When you squeeze it, it says,
复活节快乐
"Happy Easter!"
现在你挤他 他会说
Now when you squeeze him, he says,
电池液都漏出来啦 让我死了吧
"Battery acid is leaking inside of me. Let me die!"
再见
Later.
她把我最爱的棒子也拿走了
She just took my favorite stick.
管住你的女人
You need to control your woman.
你说的可是你妈
That is your mother you're talking about...
所以我管不住
so that's not happening.
我很爱阿鸡
I love Chickie.
那些东西我都很喜欢
I love all of that stuff!
我知道怎么把它弄回来
And I have a plan to get it back.
但是阿吸可能要不回来了
But maybe we'll let the Flowbee go.
好了
All right.
曼尼 按照你的请求
Manny, as requested,
我带了我最爱的小丑道具
a few of my favorite clown props.
怎么曼尼 你朋友太多[想掉粉]了吗
What's wrong, Manny, you have too many friends?
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
我自告奋勇到乔的学校游园会上表演
I volunteered to perform at Joe's school fair.
我作谢幕表演
I'm closing the show.
起码你进去的时候知道怎么回事
Well, at least you know that going in.
罐中蛇
Okay, Snakes In A Can,
无尽之帕
Endless Handkerchief,
只要你一直拉 它就会一直出来
it will keep coming out of there if you keep pulling it.
当然了 还有喷水小花
And, of course, the Squirting Flower.
太谢谢你了
Thank you so much.
在你把它们拿走之前
Before you take these from me,
要不要先喝一小杯水
would you like a small glass of water?
这是滴水杯吗
Is that a Dribble Glass?
你已经准备好了
You're ready.
不过这罐假的花生糖我还是不拿了
I think I'll pass on the fake peanut brittle, though.
它连幼儿园小孩都骗不了
It's not even fooling preschoolers.
好吧 也行
Okay, maybe.
你好 歌洛莉亚
Oh, hello, Gloria.
谢谢你招待我吃早午餐
Thank you for brunch.
非常 有颠覆性
It was... revolutionary.
是是是 再见
Yes. Goodbye.
这么难讨好
Tough room.
不不 你的领结一直转啊转的
No, no. Your bowtie is very funny
挺好玩的
because it was spinning around,
但是我总是忍不住想起
but I just can't stop thinking about
昨晚做的一个非常可怕的梦
this terrible dream that I had last night.
梦见什么了
Oh, what was it?
梦见杰了
It was about Jay.
他从很高的地方坠下来
He was falling from a great height,
而你们俩当时都站在我身边
and you both were by my side,
我很伤心 因为我知道
and I was very sad because I knew that
我再也不能见到他了
I was never, ever going to see him again.
你觉得那意味着什么
What do you think that that means?
我怎么知道 我知道的和你一样多
How would I know? I have all the same information you have.
抱歉 我得打个电话
Excuse me, I need to make a phone call.
我不知道歌洛莉亚做的恶梦
I don't know if Gloria's dreams
会不会像我的一样有预言作用
can predict the future like mine can,
但是我知道如果杰遭遇了不测
but I do know that if something happened to Jay...
我自己也活不下去了
I couldn't live with myself.
当然了我也别想活了
Of course, I wouldn't have to,
因为歌洛莉亚会杀了我
because Gloria would kill me.
杰又忘带手机了
Ay, Jay left his phone again.
小卡
Cam.
你为什么给杰打电话
Why are you calling Jay?
是吗
Am I?
我 我以为我给园丁打电话呢
I-I thought I was calling the gardener.
我忘了开院子大门
I forgot to leave the gate open,
所以我可能要回去给他开门了
so I should probably go let him in.
让凯撒再翻一次高墙太残忍了
It'd be cruel to make Caesar climb another big fence.
你知道那个动作吗
You know that maneuver
就是先一飞冲天直到失速
where you fly straight up until you stall
然后俯冲时再抬升的那种
and then pull out of the dive?
我们今天能试试吗
Can we do that today?
不行
Nope.
不用急着决定 我们先升空再说
Don't decide now. We'll talk when we're up.
杰
Hey, Jay!
杰 等一下
Jay, hey, wait up.
你觉得在他到这儿之前我们能起飞吗
Do you think we can take off before he gets here?
在他到这儿之前我们都能飞完着陆了
I think we can land before he gets here.
这是在预先检查吧
So this is a pre-check, right?
我们要检查什么
What are we looking for?
没什么
Nothing.
只是要在那群妞面前耍耍帅
Just trying to look cool for those girls over there.
杰 在你起飞之前我得先跟你谈谈
Jay, I need to talk to you before you fly.
事关生命还有
It's a matter of life and...
我的老天
Oh, good god.
卡梅隆·塔克
Cameron Tucker.
-盖斯 -你好 盖斯
- Gus. - Hi, Gus.
有什么事 小卡
What do you want, Cam?
有什么事
What do you want?
什么 对了
What? Oh, yes.
你不会想上那架飞机的
You're not gonna want to get in that plane.
歌洛莉亚做了一个很可怕的梦
Gloria had a terrible dream
梦见你从高空坠落然后摔死了
where you fell from a great height and died.
好了 盖斯 我们赶紧远走高飞
All right, Gus. Up, up, and away.
不 杰 她看上去很担忧
No, Jay, she seemed pretty upset,
而且如果梦境不幸成真了
And if something were to happen --
她老是梦见我死了
She's always dreaming about me dying.
迪迪以前也是一样一样的
Dede did the same thing.
这是妻子的典型通性
It's typical wife stuff.
-是吗 -不会有事的 小卡
- Is it? - Nothing's gonna happen, Cam.
-盖斯告诉他 -很安全的
Tell him, Gus. It's perfectly safe.
我会好好照顾他
He's in good hands.
而且你还特别强壮 我都忍不住瞄
Big hands, too -- I couldn't help but notice.
比起因为严重坠机而死
I'm more worried about
我更担心退休后无聊至死
dying from boredom in retirement than from a fiery crash.
好了 谢谢你的关心
Now, thanks for your concern.
拿好你的女士挎包 走吧
Take your purse and go.
你背的是战术挎包 对吧
That's one of those tactical totes, isn't it?
是的
Why, yes.
是的呢 盖斯
Yes, it is, Gus.
得了 走吧 小卡
Anyway, bye, Cam.
不 我哪都不去
No, you know what? I'm not going anywhere,
因为在歌洛莉亚的梦里 我是活着的
Because in Gloria's dream, I was alive.
所以如果我跟着你 这飞机就不会坠毁
So if I'm with you, this plane can't go down.
你觉得你上了这架小飞机
You think you being on this small plane
还能减小它坠毁的可能性吗
makes it less likely to crash?
别当着盖斯的面这样说我
Please don't do this to me in front of Gus, okay?
老天 我还真的是很喜欢怪物
God, I was really into trolls.
没错 尤其是你初中的舞伴 乳牙弟
Yeah, especially your junior prom date with the baby teeth.
你想干嘛
What do you want?
我得找点东西应付克拉特沃斯太太
I need to give Clutterworth something
让她别再烦我
to get her off my back.
我从没想过我会这么说
I never thought I'd say this,
但是我能问你借几件衣服吗
but can I borrow some of your clothes?
这件可以吗
What about this?
不行 不行 把它放下
Oh, no, no, no. Put that down.
-那是桑杰的衣服 -你还要留着它吗
- It's Sanjay's. - And you're gonna keep it?
我还没想好怎么处置它
I don't know what I'm gonna do with it yet.
给你这个
Here.
把它碎个稀烂
Cut it into a million pieces.
他是我第一个真正的男朋友
He was my first real boyfriend.
那又怎样 他劈腿了
So what? He cheated on you.
你得忘了他 翻篇儿过好自己的生活
You need to get over this guy and move on with your life.
我把他忘得一干二净了
I am so over him.
那你还闻什么闻
So why are you sniffing that?
我只是闻闻看他的傻气有多重
I'm just smelling how stupid he smells.
我的天
Oh, my god.
好吧 你说得对
Okay, fine. You're right.
我是得翻篇儿了
I need closure.
我在朋友圈上看到他周末回家了
I saw on Instagram he's home for the weekend.
所以呢
So...
你该拿上他的白痴连帽衫和笨鞋
You take his stupid hoodie and his clunky shoes
到他家去
and you go over there
然后把它们扔到他那张二货脸上
and throw them in his dumb face.
鞋子是我的
Those are my shoes.
妈妈 听声音浣熊好像又在打架了
Mommy, it sounds like those raccoons are fighting again.
好吧 我不吹了
Fine, I'll stop.
他懂什么艺术啊
Hey, what does he know about art?
你也看过他画的画
You've seen his drawings.
他觉得杰比一朵花还矮呢
He thinks jay is shorter than a flower.
我不懂到底怎么回事
I don't know what is happening.
我一直努力地在教她
I keep coaching her and coaching her,
可是她却吹得越来越糟了
and she's just getting worse.
我可以给她指点一二
You know what? I'll give her a few tips.
我喜欢用的管类乐器是排箫
My flute of choice has always been the Pan,
不过长笛应该也差不多
but I suppose I could dumb it down.
这简直是个噩梦
This is a nightmare.
是的 她吹得很糟糕
Yes. She's terrible.
不过真正的噩梦
But the nightmare
是梦到你老公坠亡
is seeing your husband plunging to his death
而人们觉得是你
and having people think that you did it
为了巨额保险金下的黑手
for the life insurance payout.
这倒是新鲜
That's a new detail.
歌洛莉亚 梦是预测不了未来的
Gloria, dreams don't predict the future.
那只是你脑中潜意识的反射
They're windows into the subconscious.
也许我爸从高处摔下来
Maybe falling from a great height
指的是他退休的事
is about my dad retiring.
-你真这么想 -对啊 说不定是
- You think? -Yeah, it could be.
他不再是衣柜界的巨头了
He's no longer a big shot in the closet industry,
这肯定也是件大事
which is apparently a thing.
或许你担心你们俩之间会产生隔阂
Maybe you're afraid that the two of you are growing apart.
现在就有隔阂了
It's happening already.
今天我们明明可以一起去做各种有趣的事
Today we could have done all sorts of fun things together,
他却非得去打高尔夫球
and he decided to go golfing!
我们可以去上上舞蹈课 逛逛植物园
We could have gone to dance classes, the arboretum,
或者去参观美术馆啊
the art gallery!
你说的这些更不现实
You're kind of swimming upstream with those.
你要是想让他一起做你喜欢做的事
Look. If -- if you want him to do the things that you love,
你可能要先学点他喜欢做的事
You may have to learn to do the things that he loves.
比如呢
Like what?
打高尔夫吗
Golf?
对 不然嫁给小卡吧
Yeah. Or marry Cam.
你想参加的那一切活动他都喜欢
He loves all that gay stuff you want to do.
克莱尔 等等 等等
Claire, wait, wait, wait, wait!
亲爱的
Honey.
我们还有一箱东西要捐的
We got another box of stuff to give away.
-真的吗 -对啊 把后车箱打开吧
- Really? - Yep! Pop her open.
好嘞
Okay.
话说关于阿吸你说得太对了
You were so right about the Flowbee, by the way.
它是很好 但有了它我会错过理发店的八卦
It is great, but I would miss all the gossip at the salon.
我迫不及待地想知道
I'm dying to hear
娜塔莎的雌激素贴片有没有起作用
if Natasha's estrogen patch is making a difference.
我周三见到她了 没什么变化
I saw her Wednesday. It's not.
你后面弄好了吗
Hey, you almost done back there?
我在腾点空出来
Just making some room!
你知道吗
You know what?
我很高兴能为你做这些
I am so happy to do this for you.
我爱你远远胜于爱我那台酿酒机
I love you way more than my beer making kit...
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
那个木制网球拍
the wooden tennis racket.
还有什么呢 那个牛仔帽
I don't know, the cowboy hat.
棕色那个
The brown one.
怎么还没完啊
What is taking so long?
-搞定了 -好
- All set! - Okay.
待会儿见
I'll see you guys later,
感谢你们今天帮忙收拾
and thank you so much for helping out today.
随时为您服务 克拉特沃斯夫人 亲亲双颊
At your service, Lady Clutterworth. Kiss on both cheeks.
一切如意
Bob's your uncle.
快把手举高 挥手
Keep waving up high.
举起来挥手 这样她就注意不到下面的东西了
Wave up high so she can't look down low.
-我靠... -你们开玩笑吧
- Son of a... - Seriously?
亲爱的 我们不想把这些东西捐掉
Honey, we don't want to give this stuff away.
我们很喜欢它们
We like it.
这些东西对我们很重要
It's important to us.
这些东西怎么可能对你重要了
How can it be important to you?
要不是我让你们翻箱倒柜找出来
You didn't even know it existed
你们甚至都不知道它们还在
Until I told you to go through the closet and find it.
这不是重点
That is beside the point!
所有这些东西都充满了意义
All of this stuff is packed with meaning!
真的吗 菲尔
Really, Phil?
这个廉价的雪花玻璃球对你有什么意义
What does this cheap snow globe mean to you?
那是我们在弗罗里达州的一个加油站买的
We got that at a gas station in Florida.
雪人已经融化了
The snowman's melted.
这个以前只是好玩而已
It used to just be funny,
但现在它也成了对全球变暖现象的讥讽
but now it's also a poignant statement on global warming.
是对囤物癖的讥讽还差不多
It's a poignant statement on hoarding,
我们要把它
and we are donating it
连同其他这些垃圾一起捐了
along with the rest of this junk.
真没想到你们俩还来这招
Well, I can't believe you two.
等我回去上班后 你们就知道感激我了
You'll thank me when I'm back at work
那时候我也没时间
and I don't have time
每时每刻跟在你们后面收拾烂摊子了
to be picking up after you every two minutes.
你猜怎么着
Guess what?
她没拿走我的幸运帽
She didn't get my lucky hat.
你还不如留下球拍呢
You should have kept the racket.
一起全身心投入 好吗
Let's just dive in, all right?
-我准备好了 -很好
- I'm ready! - Good.
- 好的 来一杆吧 -好
- All right, take a swing. - Okay.
看看你目前是个什么水平
Let's see what we're dealing with.
-我走到这前面... -对 是这样
- I get in front here... - Yes, you do.
然后
And then...
一 二 三
One, two, three!
球飞得好远啊
It went so far away.
我真是个天才
I am a natural.
不 他才是 你的球还在球座上没动呢
No, he is. Your ball is still on the tee.
那我比我想的还糟糕呢
I am worse than I thought then.
不 不 不 不 没事的
No, no, no, no, no. It's fine.
你只要记住一些简单的基本要领
You just need to remember a few of the simple fundamentals
我以前学的时候也很受用的
that helped me when I was learning, okay?
别担心 别担心
Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it.
先在球前面站好位置
Just line yourself up in front of the ball.
接下来你要做的就是
Now what you want to do is keep
把你的右手大拇指放在球杆的左侧
your right thumb on the left side of the shaft.
-这个拇指 -对的
- This one? - Yeah, mm-hmm.
然后低下头 好的
And then keep your head down. Okay.
-接下来左臂伸直 -好的
- Okay, and then the left arm straight... - Okay.
左手腕托起
Cup that left wrist.
我有次把脚这样放 而且
There was one time when I put the leg and --
那样没啥用
That was not helpful.
但是我觉得我想这样 不行吗
But then I feel like I want -- no?
不行 别那样做
Mm, I don't want you to do that.
-好吧 -今天不行
- Okay. - Not today.
再下来你要做的是
And then what you're gonna do
当你向上挥杆时 右手肘要保持在身体前方
is keep the right elbow in front of the body
然后转动臀部
as you swing up, and then rotate those hips.
一 二 三
One, two, three!
我的妈呀
Ay! Mama!
这球还能再打一次 回本儿了
Well, we're getting our money's worth out of that ball.
复活节快乐
Happy Easter!
阿鸡
Chickie?
我听到那声音的那一刻
The minute I heard that voice,
所有回忆都如潮水般涌入脑海
all the memories came flooding back --
大家在后院一起藏鸡蛋
Hiding eggs in the backyard,
小女孩们穿着小裙子
the girls in their dresses,
卢克穿着他的小西装
Luke in his little blazer,
菲尔则穿着 萌兔装
Phil in his...bunny suit.
复活节快乐
Happy Easter!
等下 坚持住 阿鸡
Hang on! Hang on, Chickie!
-妈妈来救你了 -复活节快乐
- Mama's coming. - Happy Easter!
等等 我来了
Hang on. I'm coming.
宝贝 我没打算把你扔掉
Baby, I didn't mean to throw you away.
-复活节快乐 -等等
- Happy Easter! - Hang on.
我听到了啦
I can hear you.
我不讨厌这件背心
I-I -- oh, I don't hate this blouse.
复活节快乐
Happy Easter!
感觉太奇怪了
This feels very weird.
但是看起来很好
Well, it looks great.
右手臂弯曲
Now hinge your right arm into an L-shape,
双手放低
Keep your hands low,
把重心转移到前脚
Shift all the weight into the front foot...
接下来要怎么做
What do I do next?
开除你的高尔夫教练
Fire your golf coach!
无意冒犯 红发
No offense, Red.
没关系 光头
None taken, Bald.
看
Here.
跟着我做
Just do what I do.
什么 变光头吗
What, lose all your hair?
抱歉 我想我有点过了
I'm sorry. I guess I was a little offended.
你喜欢跳舞吗
Do you like dancing?
喜欢啊 我跳舞
Yes, and I am much better
比这个厉害多了
doing that than doing this.
这就跟跳舞一样
Well, this is just like dancing.
把他说的全部忘掉
Forget everything he said.
只要把握节奏就行 跟我学
It's all about the rhythm. Follow me.
摆回去 挥出去
Swing back. Follow through.
摆回去
Swing back.
挥出去
Follow through.
摆回去
Swing back.
我做到了
I did it!
你被开除了 红发
You're fired, red.
平飞
Level her off.
很好
Good job.
听到了吗 完美
You hear that? Flawless.
说是我的第二天性也不为过
It makes sense this is second nature.
我已经上过很多远程操控的课程
I've logged a lot of remote-control hours.
盖斯 你说无线电遥控和真实操作
Gus, what would you say is harder,
哪个比较难
R/c or the real thing?
真实操作
The real thing.
很难决定啊
Tough call.
后面什么东西在响
What's rattling back there?
我不...
Uh, well, I don't --
我不知道这是什么玩意儿
I don't know what this thing is.
-我来处理 -收到
- My controls. - Roger that.
拖杆松了吗
That tow bar come loose?
不知道
Well, I don't know.
这
Is...
-这是拖杆吗 -是的 没错
- Is this -- is this the tow bar? - Yeah, that's it.
-抱歉 我的错 抱歉 -不不不
- Oh, ooh! Sorry, my bad. Sorry, sorry. - No, no,
没关系 我拿到了 我拿到了
That's all right. I got it. I got it.
花生糖 今天真是太幸运了
Peanut brittle, could this day get any better?
把拖杆从支架上拿开
Get the tow bar off the yoke!
不行 卡在座位中间了
No, it's stuck between the seat!
不行 算了吧 我来
I can't! Let it go! I got it!
盖斯 盖斯
Oh, Gus! Gus!
我最讨厌歌洛莉亚又说中了
I hate it when Gloria's right.
盖斯 快醒醒 盖斯 天哪 他的颧骨
Gus. Stay with us, Gus. Oh, my god. Those cheekbones.
简直跟小肯尼迪一样帅
You look like J.F.K. Jr.
他长得像小肯尼迪[死于空难]
He looks like J.F.K. Jr.!
我不知道我在干什么
I don't know what I'm doing.
开自动驾驶
Well, put it on autopilot.
-开自动驾驶 -没有自动驾驶
- Put it on autopilot! - There is no autopilot.
这就是个带翅膀的割草机而已
This is a lawnmower with wings.
你开过遥控飞机啊
You fly remote control planes!
-就按你以前那样开啊 -我把它们都撞坏了
- Do what you do there! - I crash them!
所以我才不断买新的
That's why I buy them all the time!
我错了
I was wrong.
我不想这样死掉啊
I don't want to die this way.
我宁愿平静无聊地在地上死去
I'll settle for a nice, boring death at ground level.
严格说来 我们还是会死在地上的
Well, technically, we will be dying at ground level!
我来 我来 我来
I got it! I got it! I got it!
好了
Okay.
-我们没事了 -太好了
- We're good. - Great.
就跟你说下
Just so you know
我一直都非常镇定
I completely kept my cool through that whole thing.
听我说 我知道打中几杆运气球确实感觉很好
Listen, I know it felt great to hit a couple of lucky shots.
我打了一整桶运气球呢
I hit a whole bucket of lucky shots.
但是没有学好技术
But there's a limit to how good you can get
想要进步多少就很有限
without learning the proper techniques.
我在教你...
I was trying to show you, but --
-非常好 莉莉 -你做了什么
- Very good, Lily. - What did you do?
我只告诉她忘掉一切 用心感受音乐
I just told her to forget everything and feel the music.
二爸 以后就由曼尼来教我了
Dad, Manny's gonna teach me from now on.
这是你今天第二次被开了 红发
Ay, this is the second time you got fired today, Red.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
听着 每个人学习的方式不一样
Look, everybody learns in different ways.
我这种高智商的方法不适合歌洛莉亚
My intellectual approach just wasn't right for Gloria,
可能也不适合莉莉
and it probably wasn't right for Lily.
这么说确实很惭愧
It -- it's humbling to admit,
但我就是太聪明了 不适合教人
but I'm just too smart to teach.
坚强点 我为你自豪
Be strong. I'm proud of you.
谢谢
Thanks.
很多姑娘会打扮得性感
You know, a lot of girls would have tried to look sexy
让他看看他错过了什么
to show him what he's missing.
所以呢
Is there more to that?
没有 只是想理解你的想法
No, just trying to figure you out.
你好 桑杰
Hello, Sanjay.
还是应该叫你'桑感情'呢
Or should we call you "Sans-feelings"?
重新来
Start over.
你把这个落在我家了
You left this at my house.
我本来打算把它剪得稀巴烂的
I was going to just cut it up in tiny little pieces,
但我觉得应该让你直视
but I thought you should have to
被你伤害了的人的眼睛
look into the eyes of the person you hurt.
我希望你的新女友值得让你这样做
I hope your new little girlfriend is worth it.
她不值得 那是个天大的错误
She wasn't. It was a huge mistake.
我不习惯女孩子喜欢我
I'm not used to girls liking me.
斯坦福的女孩子个个都很出众
Stanford girls are all type "A".
她们都非常咄咄逼人
They're very aggressive.
我完全傻了
I'm in way over my head.
这样咱俩就没事了吗
And that's supposed to make this okay?
不 有事
No. Nothing's okay.
我很痛苦
I'm miserable.
我每天都很想你
And I miss you every day.
说得好听
Yeah, right.
-你至于吗 -他好像很真诚啊
- Seriously? - Oh, well, he seems sincere.
没错
I am.
虽然物理定律不会允许
If I could go back in time,
但是如果能回到过去
which the laws of physics don't disallow,
我不会再伤害你了
I never would have hurt you.
如果你相信多元宇宙的话
Well, if you believe in the multi-verse,
就会有一个时空气泡 在那里
there currently exists a bubble of space-time
你没有伤害我
where you didn't.
我希望我们在那里
I wish we were there.
天哪
Oh, my God.
这就是学霸的前戏吗
Is this geek foreplay?
因为我完全听不懂
'cause I don't understand any of this.
如果你真的那么不开心 你为什么没有联系我
If you were so unhappy, why didn't you contact me?
我很羞耻 很尴尬
I was ashamed and embarrassed.
我已经打算一个人度过余生了
I came to terms with being alone for the rest of my life.
我回家过周末
I'm home for the weekend,
但我父母都不在这里
and my parents aren't even here.
-你父母不在家吗 -这话我懂
- You're parents aren't home? - That, I understand.
我回来了
I'm home!
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
你们在这啊
There they are.
我的家人
There's my family.
爸爸抱抱 小猴子
Come here, you little monkey!
不 你又输了多少钱
Ay, no. How much money did you lose?
我今天没打高尔夫
I didn't play golf today.
我学开飞机去了
I took a flying lesson.
感觉如何
Hmm? And how was that?
没什么特别的
Uneventful.
那你怎么之前没说
Why didn't you tell me about it?
我想给你个惊喜
I wanted it to be a surprise.
那我也要给你一个惊喜
Oh, well, then I have a surprise for you, too.
我去学打高尔夫了
I took a golf lesson.
开玩笑吧 为什么
You're kidding. Why?
我想跟你一起打啊
To play with you.
想都别想
That's not gonna happen.
达琳开始和小短一起打球了
Darlene started playing with Shorty.
她嘴巴说个不停
She never stops talking.
小短得故意打个曲球 好在捡球时有点清净
He had to develop a slice just to get some alone time.
那你想怎么办
So what do you want to do?
一个人开着你那小飞机吗
Fly alone in your little plane?
不 我是想找件咱们能一起做的事情
No. The whole point is to find something we can do together.
比如飞到纳帕[加州酒乡]去吃个午餐
I pictured zipping up to napa for lunch,
到赛多纳[亚利桑那印第安圣地]吃个夕阳晚餐
Sedona for a sunset dinner.
你一吃完饭就睡着了
You fall asleep after every meal.
我才不要和你一起坐飞机
I am not getting on a plane with you.
怎么会呢
That's not true.
你吃了个烤芝士三明治
You eat a grilled cheese sandwich
想走到沙发上都费劲
and you can barely make it to the couch.
甜美的烤芝士催人眠
Nothing like a grilled cheese nap.
我也不想要你到处开飞机
I don't want you flying around in a little plane, either.
这大概是我的人生梦想
Well, it's kind of my life's dream,
但如果你不愿意我做 我就不做了
but if you want me to stop, I'll do it for you.
我昨晚做了个噩梦
I had a bad dream last night.
我觉得你退休这事让我有点害怕
I think that this retirement thing is making me very scared.
我又何尝不是[加入俱乐部]
Join the club.
但别加入我的乡村俱乐部
Just not my country club.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.
你怎么知道呢
How do you know that?
我不知道 但我们双方都花了一天时间想做些
I don't. But we both spent the day trying to do something
我们认为能让对方开心的事
we thought would make the other one happy
这就是个不错的开头
and that's a pretty good start.
看来我们只要找到
I guess we just have to find something
双方都感兴趣的事
that we have in common,
可以一起规划的事情
Like a project to do together!
-我还在呢 -等等 妈妈在想事情
- Hello? - In a minute. Mommy's thinking.
克拉特沃斯跑哪儿去了
Where the hell is Clutterworth?
在贫民区把我们的记忆分发给流浪汉
On skid row giving our memories to hobos.
她把我所有旧的时尚杂志都扔了
She threw out all my old Vogues.
没有参考 我会错穿过去流行现在过时的衣服
If I don't know the past, I'm doomed to re-wear it.
老妈 这回
Mom, this time --
是你啊
Oh, it's just you.
你们好啊
Hey, party people.
你高兴个什么劲儿
Why are you so happy?
去了趟桑杰家 翻了个篇儿
Went over to Sanjay's, got a little closure.
是吗 你的衣服倒是翻出来了
Yeah? Well, some of your clothes are on inside out.
你终于出现了 你把我的杂志全扔了
There you are. You threw out all my magazines.
要不是我当时在场
Yeah, and if I hadn't been here,
你就把桑杰的套头衫扔了
you would have thrown out Sanjay's hoodie
我也就没机会把衣服还给他
and then I would have never gotten the chance to return it,
他也就没机会向我表达他的未尽之爱
and then he never would have declared his undying love for me.
没错 姐满血复活了
That's right. I'm back.
你把我的幸运棒拿走了
And you took my lucky stick.
我超喜欢那根棒棒
I love that stick.
我找到我最喜欢的石头时拿的就是那根棒棒
I was holding it when I found my favorite rock.
天啊
Oh, my god.
别告诉我你把阿石也扔了
Please tell me you didn't throw out Rocky.
没错
You're right.
你们都没错 我是个糟糕的母亲
You're all right. I'm a terrible mother.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是怎么回事
What is happening?
已经过了五点[下班时间]了吗
Is it after 5:00 already?
-你回来了 -老爸 有点不对劲
- Hey, you're back. - Dad, something's wrong.
老妈在道歉
Mom's apologizing.
我们看过表了
No, we checked.
我没能救下阿鸡
I couldn't save Chickie.
一想起还有那么多我没能救下来的
And think about all the others I didn't save --
马里布芭比 粉兔枕头
Malibu Barbie, Pink Bunny Pillow,
筋肉人阿姆斯壮
Stretch Armstrong.
慢着 你把我的筋肉人阿姆斯壮扔了
Wait. You threw away my Stretch Armstrong?
是啊 没了 它们都没了
Yes. It's gone. They are all gone.
每年的大扫除根除了
Years of stress cleaning has eradicated
一生的珍贵记忆
a lifetime of precious memories.
如果没有呢
Well, what if it hasn't?
你是在说平行于现实的另一个宇宙吗
Are you suggesting an alternate universe that parallels reality?
我是在说平行于公路的储物车库
I'm suggesting a storage unit that parallels the freeway.
天啊
Oh, my god.
都是我们的旧东西
It's all our old stuff.
我的第一辆自行车
Ah! My first bike!
-我的梵高作业 -我的第一台电话
- My Van Gogh project! - My first phone!
好的 我等丽兹·麦克奎尔接电话
Yes, I'll hold for Lizzie McGuire.
你不是都拿去捐了吗
So all of those trips to the donation bin...
有时候我没有捐成
I didn't always make it.
-你生气了吗 -太好了
- Are you mad? - It's amazing.
看到没 我管住了我的女人
See? I'm controlling my woman.
这件衣服太有范儿了
Oh, this is totally back in style.
天啊 扭扭乐
OH, my god! Twister!
我也找到了[电影《龙卷风》]
Me, too.
我很...
I'm...
没什么...
It's no...
你把身上那股子劲儿
You just take that nutty energy of yours
全都投到工作里去
and put it to good use at the office,
我们在家里等你
and we'll be waiting for you when you get home.
你知道我们报税的时候没有算这些东西了吧
You know we already claimed all this stuff on our taxes, right?
没错
There's my girl. Yeah.
虽然大费周折 但我拿回来了
It wasn't easy, but I got it!
阿鸡
Chickie!
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
有点黏
A little sticky, huh?
复活节快乐
Happy Easter!
它真的就只会说这一句吗
Oh! Is that really all it says?
我记得它还能说别的呢
I feel like it used to say more.
-复活节快乐 -老妈 别捏了
- Happy Easter! - Mom, stop squeezing it.
-我没有 我没捏它 -复活节快乐
- I'm n-- I'm not. I'm not squeezing it. - Happy Easter!
真的好吵啊
It's really annoying.
-我什么都没干 -复活节快乐
- I'm not doing anything. - Happy Easter!
-蕴含了好多回忆 -是啊
- So many good memories, though. - Yep.
复活节快乐
Happy Easter!
那东西会吵得我睡不着觉
Yeah, I-I really cannot sleep with that going on all night.
复活节快乐
Happy Easter!
-复活节快乐 -阿石 拿它做什么
- Happy Easter! - Rocky? What's that for?
你知道做什么
You know what it's for.
复活节快乐
Happy Easter!